♪ ("I GOTTA FEELING") ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT ♪
♪ LET'S LIVE IT UP ♪
♪ I GOT MY MONEY ♪
♪ LET'S SPEND IT UP ♪
♪ GO OUT AND SMASH IT ♪
♪ LIKE OH MY GOD ♪
♪ JUMP OFF THAT SOFA ♪
♪ LET'S GET GET OFF ♪
♪ I KNOW THAT
WE'LL HAVE A BALL ♪
♪ IF WE GET DOWN ♪
♪ AND GO OUT ♪
♪ AND JUST LOSE IT ALL ♪
♪ I FEEL STRESSED OUT ♪
♪ I WANNA LET IT GO ♪
♪ LET'S GO WAY OUT SPACED OUT ♪
♪ AND LOSING ALL CONTROL ♪
♪ FILL UP MY CUP ♪
♪ MAZEL TOV ♪
♪ LOOK AT HER DANCING ♪
♪ JUST TAKE IT OFF ♪
♪ LET'S PAINT THE TOWN ♪
♪ WE'LL SHUT IT DOWN ♪
♪ LET'S BURN THE ROOF ♪
♪ AND THEN WE'LL DO IT AGAIN ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, AND
DO IT, AND DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S LIVE IT UP ♪
♪ AND DO IT, AND DO IT,
AND DO IT, DO IT, DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I GOTTA FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD, GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT, HEY ♪
♪ LET'S LIVE IT UP,
LET'S LIVE IT UP ♪
♪ I GOT MY MONEY, I'M PAID ♪
♪ LET'S SPEND IT UP,
LET'S SPEND IT UP ♪
♪ GO OUT AND SMASH
IT, SMASH IT ♪
♪ LIKE OH MY GOD,
LIKE OH MY GOD ♪
♪ JUMP OFF THAT SOFA, C'MON ♪
♪ LET'S GET GET OFF ♪
♪ FILL UP MY CUP, DRINK ♪
♪ MAZEL TOV, L'CHAIM ♪
♪ LOOK AT HER DANCING,
MOVE IT, MOVE IT ♪
♪ JUST TAKE IT OFF ♪
♪ LET'S PAINT THE
TOWN, PAINT THE TOWN ♪
♪ WE'LL SHUT IT
DOWN, SHUT IT DOWN ♪
♪ LET'S BURN THE ROOF ♪
♪ AND THEN WE'LL DO IT AGAIN ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, AND
DO IT, AND DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S LIVE IT UP ♪
♪ AND DO IT, AND DO IT,
AND DO IT, DO IT, DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, LET'S DO IT ♪
♪ LET'S DO IT, DO
IT, DO IT, DO IT ♪
♪ HERE WE COME, HERE WE GO ♪
♪ WE GOTTA ROCK, ROCK,
ROCK, ROCK, ROCK ♪
♪ EASY COME, EASY GO ♪
♪ NOW WE ON TOP,
TOP, TOP, TOP, TOP ♪
♪ FEEL THE SHOT, BODY ROCK ♪
♪ ROCK IT DON'T STOP,
STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP ♪
♪ ROUND AND ROUND, UP AND DOWN ♪
♪ AROUND THE CLOCK, CLOCK,
CLOCK, CLOCK, CLOCK ♪
♪ MONDAY, TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY, AND THURSDAY ♪
♪ FRIDAY, SATURDAY,
SATURDAY TO SUNDAY ♪
♪ GET GET GET GET GET WITH US ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT WE SAY ♪
♪ PARTY EVERY DAY ♪
♪ PA PA PA PARTY EVERY DAY ♪
♪ AND I'M FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ I GOTTA FEELING OH OH ♪
♪ THAT TONIGHT'S GONNA
BE A GOOD NIGHT ♪
BE A GOOD GOOD NIGHT ♪
♪ OH OH ♪